<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DetailPage</string>
    <string name="recent_news"> Gitall Festival</string>
    <string name="in_news">Hello My name is Sheshank and i am making this in order just to learn</string>
    <string name="publish_date">13/03/2018 10:28:22</string>

    <!--detail description string-->
    <string name="introduction">IntroDuction</string>
    <string name="technology_used">Technology used</string>
    <string name="team_members">Team Members</string>


    <!-- these are project title strings -->
    <string name="title_one">Hinton</string>
    <string name="title_two">Analyst</string>


    <!-- these are project technology strings -->
    <string name="techno_one">Python,OpenCV,JavaScript,HTML,CSS,Pytorch,Dlib,Tensorflow,Keras,AWS GPU Compute EC2 Machine</string>
    <string name="techno_two">html, php, css, javascript, jquery</string>


    <!--these are project team members strings-->
    <string name="team_one">Zaid Khan,Piyush Gandhi,Romit Dhamija,Ayushi Bansal</string>
    <string name="team_two">Ayush Ghai, Aman Manocha, Sachpreet Kaur, Amarpreet Singh</string>


    <!-- these are project introduction strings -->
    <string name="intro_one">Hinton is a fake news generator (video) platform that aims to create
awareness among the society about how fake new generation is
possible and it aims to make people believe not to blindly follow
what is seen on social media platforms like Facebook or Instagram.
The main working of the project comes in form that we can alter
facial expressions in a video live upto an extent that it is very
difficult to distinguish between original and generated video.
We use ResNet34 model trained to detect 68 points facial
landmarks on the target video, pix2pix research paper for creating a
GAN that has 2 neural networks I.e a discriminator and a generator
both trained on Pytorch, Tensorflow and Keras separately for
comparisons and then combined to make the final architecture of
the pix2pix model</string>
    <string name="intro_two">Analyst is action-packed with latest SEO updates and metric analysis to help you rise
through the difficulties and hardship you generally face during your Search engine
ranking process. It takes into account analyzing your website’s usability, mobile
friendliness, technologies, social signals, visitor count and link metrics to evaluate the
end score and grade your website. Further, you can even download the generated SEO
report from your browser onto your mobile or desktop PC by just hitting the
Download Report button for easy access or even share your score on various social
media platforms.</string>
</resources>
