<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DetailPage</string>


    <!--detail description string-->
    <string name="introduction">IntroDuction</string>
    <string name="technology_used">Technology used</string>
    <string name="team_members">Team Members</string>


    <!-- these are project title strings -->
    <string name="title_one">Hinton</string>
    <string name="title_two">Analyst</string>
    <string name="title_three">Autonmont</string>
    <string name="title_four">Market BASKET ANALYSIS</string>


    <!-- these are project technology strings -->
    <string name="techno_one">Python,OpenCV,JavaScript,HTML,CSS,Pytorch</string>
    <string name="techno_two">html, php, css, javascript, jquery</string>
    <string name="techno_three">Internet of Things, Arduino, PHP, Javascript</string>
    <string name="techno_four">Java ,html, css, jsp, javascript</string>


    <!--these are project team members strings-->
    <string name="team_one">Zaid Khan,Piyush Gandhi,Romit Dhamija,Ayushi Bansal</string>
    <string name="team_two">Ayush Ghai, Aman Manocha, Sachpreet Kaur, Amarpreet Singh</string>
    <string name="team_three">Rishabh Sachdeva,  Kriti Duggal,  Anshul Gupta,  Mansi Gandhi</string>
    <string name="team_four">Taranjeet Kaur, Chanpreet Singh, Gurjyot Singh, Amitoz Kaur</string>


    <!-- these are project introduction strings -->
    <string name="intro_one">Hinton is a fake news generator (video) platform that aims to create
    awareness among the society about how fake new generation is
    possible and it aims to make people believe not to blindly follow
    what is seen on social media platforms like Facebook or Instagram.
    The main working of the project comes in form that we can alter
    facial expressions in a video live upto an extent that it is very
    difficult to distinguish between original and generated video.
    We use ResNet34 model trained to detect 68 points facial
    landmarks on the target video, pix2pix research paper for creating a
    GAN that has 2 neural networks I.e a discriminator and a generator
    both trained on Pytorch, Tensorflow and Keras separately for
    comparisons and then combined to make the final architecture of
    the pix2pix model</string>
    <string name="intro_two">Analyst is action-packed with latest SEO updates and metric analysis to help you rise
    through the difficulties and hardship you generally face during your Search engine
    ranking process. It takes into account analyzing your website’s usability, mobile
    friendliness, technologies, social signals, visitor count and link metrics to evaluate the
    end score and grade your website. Further, you can even download the generated SEO
    report from your browser onto your mobile or desktop PC by just hitting the
    Download Report button for easy access or even share your score on various social
    media platforms.</string>
    <string name="intro_three">Automation and Real Time Monitoring are now becoming an integral part of every industrial
        setup. This project proposes an IOT (Internet of Things) based real-time monitoring and automation system
        for a prototype of an industrial setup. This system allows the operator/manager/owner of the plant to monitor
        and control the various industrial appliances of the plant remotely through an interactive web application.
        It also provides various security features, enhances the efficiency of the plant and stores the activities
        of the industrial setup in an extensive database. This project uses Arduino Uno that interfaces with the
        hardware components of the industrial setup and an IOT based Wi-Fi chip known as BOLT to connect the setup to
        the internet through the BOLT cloud. The web application is made totally responsive so as to access the system
        from any internet enabled device and in order to provide fast delivery of any emergency action.
        The major aim of this project is to demonstrate the effectiveness of an IOT based system in increasing the
        security, minimizing the power consumption, providing real time analysis and providing remote access to the
        physical system of the industrial setup using an alternate source of energy.</string>
    <string name="intro_four">Market Basket Analysis is a modelling technique based upon the theory that if you buy a
        certain group of items, you are more (or less) likely to buy another group of items. Market Basket Analysis is one
        of the most common and useful types of data analysis for marketing and retailing. It checks the items that
        are frequently purchased by customers and offers are send to that customer related to that particular item
        that is frequently purchased through SMPT protocol. In this we are using AR(association Rule).
        AR (Association Rules) is a powerful technique that can search through very large sets of seemingly random
        data to identify various types of patterns.The purpose of market basket analysis is to determine what products
        customers purchase together.  It takes its name from the idea of customers throwing all their purchases into a
        shopping cart (a "market basket") during grocery shopping.</string>

</resources>
